

IGNACIO FRIED

PROFILE

Well organized, creative, and proven marketing professional. Experience working with and across sales teams and well as external clients and agencies on creative, editorial, strategic, and tactical levels. Significant negotiation experience. Track record of delivering unique and effective content. Impressive history of planning and executing marketing campaigns.

CONTACT

PHONE: (716) 555-0100

LINKEDIN: www.linkedin.com/in/i.fried

EMAIL i.fried@live.com

SKILLS



WORK EXPERIENCE

MARKETING CONSULTANT VANARSDEL LTD, SNIPTOWN, MASSACHUSETTS SEPTEMBER 2016-PRESENT

Work with clients to craft the messaging and implement strategic positioning in their market. Assist clients with business plan, branding, advertising, remodeling, and marketing. Over a ten-month period, these efforts boosted monthly sales from \$8,000 to \$25,000. Devised and implemented social media campaign that increased brand awareness by 125% on average. Program resulted in a dramatic \$50,000 increase in internet sales. Create marketing campaigns including email, print, digital, outdoor, and social media. Based on market analysis, craft concept and content for journal ads, direct mail campaigns and blogs.

MARKETING SPECIALIST LUCERNE PUBLISHING, BOSTON, MASSACHUSETTS JUNE 2013-AUGUST 2016

Co-managed the development and delivery of the design language for a companywide media kit for all company projects, increasing national sales by 8%. Coordinated and across multiple departments internally and collaborate with external IT and other professional consultants to design, build, and launch ten websites for ten company brands. Developed SEO optimized content for numerous in-house websites, blog posts and social media platforms. Several of my articles were picked up by major media outlets. Kept current with marketing strategies and developed social media campaigns to increase brand influence.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN ART AND DESIGN SCHOOL OF FINE ART, MOPTON, MASSACHUSETTS 2009–2013